

ABOUT ME

A Cyber Security enthusiast and researcher, who tries to achieve the highest standard possible at any given risk. Interested in exploring and making tools, scripting and development, CTFs, Bug Hunting, Pentesting, Reverse Engineering, etc. A coffee lover who is looking forward towards a career in Web or Mobile Security testing.

MY CONTACT

Phone:

+91 9633 253 253

Email:

sejoynerjoy@gmail.com

Website:

https://c0ff33b34n.github.io/

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sejoynerjoy-00b448193

Address:

Kannampilly (H), North Chalakudy, 680 307

SEJOYNER JOY

PENTESTER

WORK EXPERIENCES

- Cyber Security Analyst | ValueMentor
- June 2022 till date
- Security Analyst, Penetration tester
- Web, API, Mobile (Android, iOS), Cloud, Network VAPT

• Cyber Security Analyst | Industrus Tech

- Security Analyst, Penetration tester, Instructor
- Sept 2021 June 2022
- Trained 500+ students on web security

Security Researcher at Intigriti and many VDPs

- Reported bugs and vulnerabilities in different platforms.
- Speaker at Initcrew community about Web Penetration testing.
- Active hunter at RedBull, found different bugs and got swags.

• IEEE Volunteer (2018 - 2022)

- Web Master, Security Tester, LINK Representative
- Participated and organized many IEEE events.

ACHIEVEMENTS

CEH Certified

- Certified Ethical Hacker from EC-Council (v11)

HALL OF FAME

- United Nations, Inflectra.com, Nokia, Surf.nl, etc.

HackTheBox

- Got Rank: 300 all over the world. Badge - Elite Hacker

HackerRank

- Got Rank: 1 all over the world in Python and Linux Shell (Bash).

Intigriti

- Got Rank: 280 all over the world.

SKILLS AND HOBBIES

- **# Penetration Testing**
- # Web VAPT
- # Mobile VAPT
- # BurpSuite, Postman
- # Linux
- # CTFs
- # Bug Hunting
- # Dorking
- # Python, Bash
- # Nessus, Acunetix
- # MobSF
- **# PT Automation**
- # HTML, CSS, JS

EDUCATION

- Sahrdaya College of Engineering and Technology
- B.Tech | Computer Science (2018 2022)
- Taking up specialization courses in Cyber Security to broaden skill set.
- Done different projects for Security Testing.

• St. Joseph's EMHSS, Aloor

- XII Computer Science Enrolled since 2016 to 2018
- X Completed in 2016